https://www.telxl.com/privacy-policy/

447
page-template-default,page,page-id-447,qode-quick-links-1.0,ajax_fade,page_not_loaded,,qode_popup_menu_push_text_right,qode-child-theme-ver-1.0.0,qode-theme-ver-11.0,qode-theme-bridge,wpb-js-composer js-comp-ver-6.2.0,vc_responsive
TELXL LIMITED PRIVACY POLICY
Introduction
TelXL Ltd respects your privacy and we will only use your information in the way we have described in this policy. When using your information we aim to be fair and transparent, and to follow our obligations under UK data protection laws.
The policy also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information; how you can access / update this information and procedures we have in place to safeguard it.
TelXL Ltd is a data controller and processor for the purposes of GDPR and the Data Protection Act 2018. Our address is Unit 3 Centech Park, Fringe Meadow Road, North Moons Moat, Redditch B98 9NR. Our business contact details for privacy and data are: email support@telxl.com, phone number 03700 670 670.
What does the Privacy Policy cover?
Our Privacy Policy covers how TelXL Ltd handles your personal information. The policy covers personal information obtained through:
An enquiry made to obtain information from our website (www.telxl.com) or by speaking with a TelXL Ltd employee;
Telephone or email contact made to discuss a new service opportunity;
Telephone or email contact made to discuss an existing service;
Registering (via a consent form) for more information, having made initial contact at a conference / seminar or exhibition;
The normal operation of our call management functionality, supported by an Agreement;
The normal operation of an App to make and receive telephone calls.
Information that we collect
We will ask for the minimum information that enables us to provide a service or service information and we are likely to collect this information by email, telephone, letter, tender or RFP documentation, consented request for information documentation or through an information request via our website. The information we collect may include name, business address, contact telephone numbers and email address. We may ask for or collect bank account details or credit card details to facilitate the payment of invoices and to operate credit card services, including Direct Debit.
If you become a user of TelXL Ltd services and contract for credit card payment services, the card data is processed by one of our hosted partner PCI Level 1 systems, using a ‘token’ exchange to identify card details with the payment processor. The ‘token’ and not the actual card details, is populated in the company database meaning that the sensitive card details are only stored on the payment service provider’s highly secure PCI-DSS compliant systems.
Once you become a user of TelXL Ltd services and the service receives a telephone call we will keep a record of that call, including the called number, irrespective of whether the call is successful or fails for any reason. We capture information relating to how long or how frequently you use our services (call durations) and may use this information for invoicing or contracted services. Our company website doesn’t use cookies to track our customers.
If you become a user of TelXL Ltd services and contract for call recording facilities, we will record the calls you specify and store the associated audio files securely on our operational platforms for the period specified in your service contract and thereafter transport them to the storage destination of your choice as predetermined by you.
If you become a user of TelXL Ltd services we will create and store login information for you and your users to access the services for which you have contracted. This information will allow you and your users to access telephony management services and stored management information. All login activity is password protected and after initial service setup / initial user change, password details are no longer visible to TelXL Ltd personnel with access control passed to individual user accounts.
When connecting to the TelXL website (telxl.com) we may collect information relating to your IP address and the type of browser being used for access.
Do we share your information with anyone else?
We will only share your information when formally requested to do so by:
Regulatory agencies – e.g. OFCOM;
Emergency Services – e.g. Police, Fire & Rescue, Ambulance and Trading Standards, related to the detection of crime, the apprehension or prosecution of offenders or related to emergency situations either historical or active;
Other Government Authorities
Agencies tasked with safeguarding national security.
We do not share your information with any commercial organisations.
How long do we store your personal information?
We only retain your personal information for the duration necessary to operate the service or the service contract period or until receipt of a formal request to destroy any or all information or for 12-months whichever is the longest.
We do not store, process or transmit for storage or processing any personal information outside of the UK.
Some data that might be considered personal is retained as required by Regulation, Emergency and Security Services, such as service users details, caller and dialled number call details.
Data Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and when we store and process it in our data centres. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and do not take responsibility for any third-party actions when we have endeavoured to follow generally accepted standards. In addition, we do not take responsibility for your systems, the Internet itself or any third-party networks or services used to transmit data which are outside the firewall of the data centres we use to process and store your personal data. If you have any questions about the security of our services, please contact us.
We are ISO27001 and Cyber Security compliant.
How do we use the information we collect?
We use the information we collect from all our services to provide, support, maintain, protect and improve service delivery to new and potential clients, for the purposes of accurate invoicing, for the investigation of disputes and to expand the TelXL Ltd client base through securing new contracts.
TelXL Ltd does not sell personal information to any individual or organisation. Any information, purchased by TelXL Ltd, for marketing purposes is limited to contact details at an organisational level and does not contain personal details about personnel employed by that organisation.
Your rights
You may ask us not to process your information for marketing purposes.
You are entitled to a copy of the information we hold about you, and to ask us to correct any inaccuracies.
You may ask us to stop using your information, and to delete it, although we may maintain a skeleton set of your information for regulation and legal purposes. If you ask us to do this we will not be able to continue our contract with you.
We will respond to your request within 30 days.
You may make a complaint to the Information Commissioner (www.ico.org.uk).
Other Websites
Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of TelXL. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their Privacy Policies. We encourage you to carefully read the Privacy Policy of any website you visit.
Updates to the Privacy Policy
TelXL may update this Privacy Policy and we will place a notice on our website or within our solutions when doing so. We reserve the right to amend our Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Data Collected through TelXL Purchased Solutions
TelXL is in the business of providing Contact-Centre-as-a-Service (CCaaS) solutions and associated services and in connection with providing such offerings to its customers. TelXL collects information (including personal information) under the direction of its customers about their business activities, employees, contractors, affiliates, and applicants (“Customer Data”). TelXL has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes and stores for TelXL customers and TelXL will process, store and retain Customer Data as per our agreement with our applicable customer (including transferring the Customer Data to the applicable customer). Therefore, if you are an employee/contractor/applicant of one of our customers, and would no longer like to be involved with one of our customers that use our solutions or otherwise have issues related to your data that is included in Customer Data (such as to correct, amend, or delete such data), please contact the customer that you interact with directly. For the purposes of the EU-US Privacy Shield, the Swiss Privacy Shield and other global privacy laws, TelXL acts as a processor/instruction taker which accesses and processes Customer Data on behalf of its customers, which are the controller/owner of such data. If the response from directly contacting the customer is unreasonable, please contact TelXL and we will assist.
TelXL are the UK's leading telecommunications supplier of wholesale real-time intelligent network based solutions to the reseller community.
©2002-17 TelXL Limited All rights reserved. E&OE. – Privacy Policy
